http://www.bartinst.com/pages/privacy_policy

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. It is Bartlett Instrument Co.'s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, http://www.bartinst.com, and other sites we own and operate.
Information Collection and Use
We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.
We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
For a better experience, while using our website, we may require you to provide us with certain
personally identifiable information, including but not limited to email, name. The information that we request will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy.
The app does use third party services, like Google Analytics that may collect information used to identify you.
We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.
You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.
Links to Other Sites
Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.
This website may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed
to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly
advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over
and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites
or services.
Children’s Privacy This website does not address anyone under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect
personally identifiable information from children under 18. In the case we discover that a child
under 18 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from
our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal
information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.
Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review
this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting
the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on
this page.
This policy is effective as of 17 September 2019.
Contact Us
Please refer to our Contact Us page to find phone, email and postal addresses for Bartlett Instrument Co. If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, sales, our mobile applications or anything else.
We pride ourselves in quality products & service.
We use cookies to improve your experience on our site. To find out more, read our privacy policy and/or cookie policy.
Sounds good, I want a better experience.
Other Options
